(Leonard:)- What's up?
- Well, tonight's my date with Penny.
And we haven't been able to connect
by phone...
- Yeah, I'm sorry. It's been broken.
- Or e-mail.
Yeah, that's broken too.
Everything's broken.
(Stuart:)Anyway, I was just wondering
if you had any last-minute advice.
(Leonard:)All right. Well, off the top of my head...
...you know, I think the most important
thing with Penny is to go really slow.
(Leonard:)I mean, glacial.
(Leonard:)- Okay.
- You know, guys come on to her...
(Leonard:)...all the time, so you need to, like,
set yourself apart, you know?
(Leonard:)Be a little shy.
And don't make too much eye contact.
(Leonard:)And you know, treat her with, like,
cool detachment.
(Leonard:)And, you know, fear.
- Fear?
LEONARD: Yeah.
(Leonard:)Like you're afraid
that if you touch her, she'll break.
(Stuart:)Well,
that plays right into my wheelhouse.
(Leonard:)Good, good.
Well, you kids have fun tonight.